Hello, its me, Michelin star, Chef Chef Kilian
misting the channel once again.
sorry about the uh, pixelated face,
it's not a camera effect, this is what i look like
after some crabs wanted revenge
the last time I was here, I showed you how to prepare
a famous, French, shellfish dish.
Then I got this comment that bothered me.
like, I'm happy he wants me to show off another country's food.
But I'm sad that he's not confident in
in the culinary culture of Italy!
So I have decided to answer this nice comment
by making the traditional Italiano dish:
Pit-ih-izza
well, first question i have to ask you though,
I know I've said this before but
what's this? A pineapple?
a pilo-de-pina?
well in southern Italy, It's reffered to as a pizza
without bread, sauce, and cheese.
Pizza Hawaiino, something so tasty, king Kamehameha
of the sandwich islands, named his kingdom after it.
According to legend, when Europeans
first encountered it in modern day Paraguay
they said, "this belongs to that one dish from Naples."
and i-i feel like
most of us today could not imagine a
slice without this fruity goodness.
Since we already have the main ingredient,
the other things we need to make is dough,
sauce, cheese, and toppings.
We will actually start with the sauce. The main ingredient
in pizza sauce is
is this Mexican dish named tomatoes.
These need to be pureed.
Hey! Chef Kilian! Can I buy pre-pureed tomatoes?
Sure you can!
You f***ing casual.
Uh why even make-a the pizza
Uh why not go and order one from Hutte-the-pizza
You can't just through the tomatoes in the pot,
because they are beautiful but
they need to know that.
You have to tell every tomato its beautiful.
Now, I am attached to them.
But, I have to say goodbye.
*Sadly singing Andrea Boceli's Con Te Partiro*
Now its mush! Time to add
pepperoni,
garlic-o,
oregano-ne,
Parpelona Onion
Olive oil, extra social awkward
Boil!
So its done!
Now lets
taste this
mmm
DISGOSTING
I WOULDN'T FEED THIS TO MY FICTIONAL
ITALIAN GRANDMOTHER'S GRAVE.
Its missing that ingredient that makes pizza special
-"Chef Kilian, is it pineapple?"
Its pineapple!! Can't just pour pineapple pieces into it,
it would destroy the consistency.
I had no other choice.
I had to do it.
I went out, and I
bought a
PINEAPPLE SMOOTHIE
just merged the tomatoes with the sweet
Juices!!!!
mmmm
Now its actually edible.
Step two bread
we need yeast. I'm assuming all of you
have your own home-grown yeast?
Well,
Throw it out the Window! Real Pizza can only be made
with 500 year old, Southern Italian yeast.
I personally recommend walking down to Naples and
scrape some of it off the walls of the Catacombs.
What we need now is
cocaine of the baking
Salt-o
Spring water, shipped all the way from Italy
And I learned from my earlier mistake with the sauce
so I dried some pineapple over night
to bake it into the bread.
Now put the three things into the flour bag and we should have
pizza dough. Just not Italian pizza dough
This is why we had to make the sauce first instead of now.
While the bread is rising
we need to sing Italian Opera to it.
For three hours. Minimum.
The sound waves will turn the bread Italian
*clears throat*
*sings generic Italian song, cant tell which with how short it is*
*sings faster paced generic Italian song*
*singing the end of the barber of seville largo al factotum*
*singing bella note from Lady and the Tramp*
Wait a minute!
*panting* This
this isn't Italian opera!
This is Disney!
D-Did I ruin it?
No,
It
It-
Very close.
Real Naples chefs do this for 24 hours.
Time to decide topping.
Canned pineapple or fresh pineapple?
Both, of course.
The other topping is ham
-"AH Chef Kilian!
Let me guess:
Maybe some ham from a can?
WHAT.
THE
F***
I would never!
Disrespect the Italian kitchen like that!
I have bought Prosciutto di marca generica
Tuscan ham thats matured for three years- it- it's actually
200 dollar ham. For my pineapple pizza.
The only one ingredient left is the cheese.
How do we make mozzarella?
or in Italian: mozzarella
It's actually very easy,
and very Italian.
You pour some milk,
and then you guilt the milk
until the guilt causes it to collapse into mozzarella.
Leche,
you come here
on the day I make-e the pizza
and you are not meltable cheese.
This,
breaks my heart
but I can take it
for I am a man.
but, ah
the cow you were milked from,
hearing of this,
it will kill her.
Now, we're in the finale.
Make the shape.
You have to do This because Naples-
uh oh
I did it but dried pineapple, it was the bane of my existence,
So this will be a THICCC pizza
Now, we are supposed to smear olive oil on it,
but what if, we instead, hear me out:
use pineapple juice.
place the sauce-ini,
toppings first, I'm using an electric oven
so I need to bake it before applying cheese.
Otherwise, it will turn dry, like a *laughing* Roman pizza
After the oven apply the cheese,
and now finally we need to apply the basil.
To make it as fresh and earthy as possible,
just grab the plant, along with the earth
through some earth in there for good measure,
in the oven,
and its Done!
And thats pizza Hawaiino!
look at that!
when you see this thing,
a portion,
of Kilian's audience,
the largest portion, in fact,
we're not gonna name their names,
but they Will say something like:
"What in tarnation???
That's not a patza!
A patza,
is fifty percent bread,
49 percent cheese,
and one percent rest of the shingamading.
And twenty percent sauce.
Come to my hometown of CHIIIICAHGO
and I'll show you a real Patza!
While everyone was listening to that perfect impersonation of what literally all of them sound like,
I ran out and got some Italian wine.
Wine glasses are in the sink,
but I bought one of those "one glass size fits all alcohols" glass
The wine smells delicous,
like it comes from the second best wine producing country in Europe.
Like-like it even smells like silver metal.
Now lets taste the THICCC pizza.
And my liable opinion:
It's quite f***ing disgusting.
I am a hard self-critic, but thinking back, it was perfect.
I give it a ten out of ten.
It's really true, that old saying about Swedes and Italians:
Italians make way better food,
but we, are way better,
at football.
Thank you for watching,
Thank you, Kilian Experience, who I am completely unrelated to,
for having me on,
final words:
All you need to be a real chef,
is chef's clothing,
and temporary insanity.